recipesthatcrock.com 2019-12-09

# Disclosure, Disclaimer & Privacy Policies - Recipes That Crock!

## Disclosure Information

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me, Aunt Lou and occasionally Puddie. (We don’t have a staff)  For questions about this blog, please contact [cris@recipesthatcrock.com](mailto:cris@recipesthatcrock.com) .

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, or other forms of compensation, such as free products to review and giveaway. (Mama likes to pay the bills and the fam likes free stuff)

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity.  (Not here to trick anyone) The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. (Sometimes I am going to post about that awesome free stuff) That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content. (Not going to hide it, yo)

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics (Dude, I gots opinions and if they are going to pay me for it, don’t hate). Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products (I’ve said it a million times, I don’t post what I don’t believe in. I have had to turn down products in the past and don’t hesitate to do so, yo). The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own (I am my own woman, ya hear *shakes fist in air sarcastically*). Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.(I am not an expert or a salesman… have your people call their people… remember, I don’t gots people ;))

The owner(s) of this blog would like to disclose the following existing relationships (my peeps). These are companies, organizations or individuals that may have a significant impact on the content of this blog (cause I love ‘em). I was raised on a farm and very much support today’s farmers. Additionally, I am employed by and/or consult with various farm related organizations including Indiana Family of Farmers and it’s associated organizations. This association just so happens to go very well with my love of food and truth be told, yours too 

Additional ongoing relationships include:

  * I am a head over heels fan of Gooseberry Patch Cookbooks, and I often receive free cookbooks from them for myself and to give away in exchange for my honest review. (Dude, GP is awesome and they have blessed me with a lot of cookbook giveaways for you… say it with me… Mommy Score!)
  * All links to Amazon products on this blog are affiliate links. (We also heart Amazon and great prices! We shop and find great deals, share them with you,  you shop and we get a percentage (at no cost to you) so we can shop some more… it is an awesome circle of shoppiness!)

To get your own policy(sans the common sense commentary), go to [https://www.disclosurepolicy.org](https://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)

## Disclaimer

All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) provides this website as a service.

While the information contained within the site is periodically updated, no guarantee is given that the information provided in this website is correct, complete, and/or up-to-date.

The materials contained on this website are provided for general information purposes only and do not constitute legal or other professional advice on any subject matter.

All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) does not accept any responsibility for any loss which may arise from reliance on information contained on this site.

The contents of this site are protected by copyright under international conventions and, apart from the permission stated, the reproduction, permanent storage, or retransmission of the contents of this site is prohibited without the prior written consent of All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com).

Some links within this website may lead to other websites, including those operated and maintained by third parties.

All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) includes these links solely as a convenience to you, and the presence of such a link does not imply a responsibility for the linked site or an endorsement of the linked site, its operator, or its contents.

This website and its contents are provided “AS IS” without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement.

Reproduction, distribution, republication, and/or retransmission of material contained within this website are prohibited unless the prior written permission of All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) has been obtained.

## Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com), as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers’, consumers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our website.

 **Personal Information**

All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold to third parties.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers who to our knowledge may collect personal information as follows:

  * Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.
  * Google Search – the search box on this web site (“Search Box”) is powered by Google Inc (“Google”). You acknowledge and agree that Google’s privacy policy (located at <https://www.google.com/privacy.html>) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.
  * MailChimp/Mailer Lite – these services are used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. They store your provided name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications upon your request when you signed up for the service.  Please refer to the MailChimp and/or Mailer Lite privacy policies for further information.
  * MiloTree – this service connects users to our social media profiles and tracks clicks and subscriptions. Please refer to the MiloTree privacy policies for further information.

This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

 **Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DoubleClick cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn’t cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

 **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

 **Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

 **Release of Information**

If All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com or GOODEnessGracious.com) is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

 **How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please contact us at cris@recipesthatcrock.com.

 **Updates and Effective Date**

All Goode Media, LLC (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

 **Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to All Goode Media, LLC’s (including RecipesThatCrock.com and GOODEnessGracious.com) Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

 _This page was updated May 2018 and overrides any previous policies._
